http://www.zeroc.com/terms-of-use

Fork me on GitHubTerms of UseLast Update: July 21, 2017
Please read these Terms of Use carefully before using this web site. If you do not agree to these Terms, then please do not use this site.
Welcome to the ZeroC web site (the "Site"). Through the Site, you have access to a variety of resources and content. These include: (a) software ("Software"); (b) web pages, data, messages, text, images, photographs, graphics, audio and video such as podcasts and screencasts, and documents such as white papers and product documentation ("Materials"); and (c) forums, blogs, e-mail functions, and other services in connection with which you can upload, download, share, email, post, publish, transmit or otherwise access or make available Content (as defined below) ("Community Services").
Software, Materials, Community Services, and other information, content and services are collectively referred to as "Content." By accessing or using the Site or the Content provided on or through the Site, you agree to follow and be bound by the following terms and conditions concerning your access to and use of the Site and the Content provided on or through the Site ("Terms of Use") and our Privacy Policy. ZeroC, Inc. and its affiliated companies ("We" or "ZeroC") may revise the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy at any time without notice to you. The revised Terms of Use and Privacy Policy will be effective when posted. You can review the most current Terms of Use at https://zeroc.com/terms-of-use and Privacy Policy at https://zeroc.com/privacy.
1. Terms Applicable to Specific Content and Areas of the Site
Some areas of the Site or Content provided on or through the Site may have additional rules, guidelines, license agreements, user agreements or other terms and conditions that apply to your access or use of that area of the Site or Content (including terms and conditions applicable to a corporation or other organization and its users). If there is a conflict or inconsistency between the Terms of Use and the rules, guidelines, license agreement, user agreement or other terms and conditions for a specific area of the Site or for specific Content, the latter shall have precedence with respect to your access and use of that area of the Site or Content.
2. Use of Software
Your use of Software is subject to all agreements such as a license agreement or user agreement that accompanies or is included with the Software, ordering documents, exhibits, and other terms and conditions that apply ("License Terms"). In the event that Software is provided on or through the Site and is not licensed for your use through License Terms specific to the Software, you may use the Software subject to the terms of the GNU General Public License v2.
3. Use of Materials
You may download, store, display on your computer, view, listen to, play and print Materials that ZeroC publishes or broadcasts on the Site or makes available for download through the Site subject to the following: (a) the Materials may be used solely for your personal, informational, noncommercial purposes; (b) the Materials may not be modified or altered in any way; and (c) the Materials may not be redistributed.
4. Use of Community Services
Community Services are provided as a convenience to users and ZeroC is not obligated to provide any technical support for, or participate in, Community Services. While Community Services may include information regarding ZeroC products and services, including information from ZeroC employees, they are not an official customer support channel for ZeroC.
You may use Community Services subject to the following: (a) Community Services may be used solely for your personal, informational, noncommercial purposes; (b) Content provided on or through Community Services may not be redistributed; and (c) personal data about other users may not be stored or collected except where expressly authorized by ZeroC.
5. Reservation of Rights
The Site and Content provided on or through the Site are the intellectual property and copyrighted works of ZeroC or a third party provider. All rights, title and interest not expressly granted with respect to the Site and Content provided on or through the Site are reserved. All Content is provided on an "As Is" and "As Available" basis, and ZeroC reserves the right to terminate the permissions granted to you in Sections 2, 3 and 4 above and your use of the Content at any time.
6. Your Content
You agree that you will only upload, share, post, publish, transmit, or otherwise make available ("Share") on or through the Site Content that you have the right and authority to Share. You agree that you will not Share any Content that: (a) is binary executable code; (b) is false or misleading; (c) is defamatory, derogatory, degrading or harassing of another or constitutes a personal attack; (d) invades another's privacy or includes another's confidential, sensitive or personal information; (e) promotes bigotry, racism, hatred or harm against any group or individual; (f) is obscene or not in good taste; (g) violates or infringes or promotes the violation or infringement of another's rights, including intellectual property rights; (h) you do not have the right and authority to Share; (i) violates or promotes the violation of any applicable laws or regulations; (j) contains a solicitation of funds, goods or services, or promotes or advertises goods or services; or (k) contains any viruses, Trojan horses, or other components designed to limit or harm the functionality of a computer.
ZeroC does not want to receive confidential information from you through or in connection with the Site. Notwithstanding anything that you may note or state in connection with Sharing Content, it shall not be considered confidential information and shall be received and treated by ZeroC on a non-confidential and unrestricted basis.
7. No Unlawful or Prohibited Use
You agree not to use the Site or Content provided on or through the Site for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these Terms of Use, or the rules, guidelines or terms of use posted for a specific area of the Site or Content provided on or through the Site.
8. Indemnity
You agree to indemnify and hold harmless ZeroC, its officers, directors, employees and agents from and against any and all claims, liabilities, damages, losses or expenses, including reasonable attorneys' fees and costs, due to or arising out of Content that you Share, your violation of the Terms of Use or any additional rules, guidelines or terms of use posted for a specific area of the Site or Content provided on or through the Site, or your violation or infringement of any third party rights.
9. Monitoring
ZeroC has no obligation to monitor the Site or screen Content that is Shared on or through the Site. However, ZeroC reserves the right to review the Site and Content and to monitor all use of and activity on the Site, and to remove or choose not to make available on or through the Site any Content at its sole discretion.
10. Termination of Use
ZeroC may, in its sole discretion, at any time discontinue providing or limit access to the Site, any areas of the Site or Content provided on or through the Site. You agree that ZeroC may, in its sole discretion, at any time, terminate or limit your access to or use of the Site or any Content. ZeroC will terminate or limit your access to or use of the Site if, under appropriate circumstances, you are determined to be a repeat infringer of third party copyright rights. You agree that ZeroC shall not be liable to you or any third-party for any termination or limitation of your access to or use of the Site or any Content.
11. Disclaimer
EXCEPT WHERE EXPRESSLY PROVIDED OTHERWISE, THE SITE, AND ALL CONTENT PROVIDED ON OR THROUGH THE SITE, ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS. ZEROC EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT WITH RESPECT TO THE SITE AND ALL CONTENT PROVIDED ON OR THROUGH THE SITE. ZEROC MAKES NO WARRANTY THAT: (A) THE SITE OR CONTENT WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS; (B) THE SITE WILL BE AVAILABLE ON AN UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, SECURE, OR ERROR-FREE BASIS; (C) THE RESULTS THAT MAY BE OBTAINED FROM THE USE OF THE SITE OR ANY CONTENT PROVIDED ON OR THROUGH THE SITE WILL BE ACCURATE OR RELIABLE; OR (D) THE QUALITY OF ANY CONTENT PURCHASED OR OBTAINED BY YOU ON OR THROUGH THE SITE WILL MEET YOUR EXPECTATIONS.
ANY CONTENT ACCESSED, DOWNLOADED OR OTHERWISE OBTAINED ON OR THROUGH THE USE OF THE SITE IS USED AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK. ZEROC SHALL HAVE NO RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OR USE OF CONTENT.
ZEROC RESERVES THE RIGHT TO MAKE CHANGES OR UPDATES TO, AND MONITOR THE USE OF, THE SITE AND CONTENT PROVIDED ON OR THROUGH THE SITE AT ANY TIME WITHOUT NOTICE.
12. Limitation of Liability
IN NO EVENT SHALL ZEROC BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, OR DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, REVENUE, DATA OR USE, INCURRED BY YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION IN CONTRACT OR TORT, ARISING FROM YOUR ACCESS TO, OR USE OF, THE SITE OR ANY CONTENT PROVIDED ON OR THROUGH THE SITE.
13. Exclusions and Limitations
SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE DISCLAIMER OR EXCLUSION OF CERTAIN WARRANTIES OR THE DISCLAIMER, EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF CERTAIN LIABILITIES. TO THE EXTENT THAT THEY ARE HELD TO BE LEGALLY INVALID, DISCLAIMERS, EXCLUSIONS AND LIMITATIONS SET FORTH IN THESE TERMS OF USE, INCLUDING THOSE SET FORTH IN SECTIONS 12 AND 13, DO NOT APPLY AND ALL OTHER TERMS SHALL REMAIN IN FULL FORCE AND EFFECT.
14. Privacy Policy
ZeroC is concerned about your privacy and has developed a policy to address privacy concerns. For more information, please see ZeroC's Privacy Policy. Any personal information collected on this Site may be accessed and stored globally and will be treated in accordance with ZeroC's Privacy Policy.
15. Note About Minors
Minors are not eligible to use the Site, and we ask that they do not submit any information to us.
16. Export Restrictions/Legal Compliance
You may not access, download, use or export the Site, or the Content provided on or through the Site, in violation of any U.S. or foreign export control laws, rules and regulations (collectively, Export Control Laws), or in violation of any other applicable laws or regulations. You agree to comply with all export laws and restrictions and regulations of any United States or foreign agency or authority, and not to directly or indirectly provide or otherwise make available the products and services of ZeroC in violation of any such restrictions, laws or regulations, or without all necessary approvals, including, without limitation, for military purposes or for the development, design, manufacture or production of nuclear, chemical or biological weapons of mass destruction or of missile technology. As applicable, you shall obtain and bear all expenses relating to any necessary licenses and/or exemptions with respect to your own use of the products and services of ZeroC outside the U.S. Neither the products of ZeroC nor the underlying information or technology may be downloaded or otherwise provided or made available, either directly or indirectly, (a) into any country listed in Country Group E of Supplement No.1 to Part 740 of the Export Administration Regulations (currently: Cuba, North Korea, Iran, Sudan and Syria), any other country subject to U.S. trade sanctions, to individuals or entities controlled by such countries, or to nationals or residents of such countries other than nationals who are lawfully admitted permanent residents of countries not subject to such sanctions; or (b) to anyone listed on any of the prohibited persons lists published by the U.S. government, including the Specially Designated Nationals list. By agreeing to these Terms of Use, you agree to the foregoing and represent and warrant that you are not located in, under the control of, or a national or resident of any such country or on any such list.
17. Applicable Laws
All matters relating to your access to, and use of, the Site and Content provided on or through or uploaded to the Site shall be governed by U.S. federal law or the laws of the State of Delaware. Any legal action or proceeding relating to your access to, or use of, the Site or Content shall be instituted in a state or federal court in Delaware. You and ZeroC agree to submit to the jurisdiction of, and agree that venue is proper in, these courts in any such legal action or proceeding.
18. Copyright/Trademark
Copyright © 2017, ZeroC, Inc. All rights reserved.
ZeroC, Ice, the Internet Communications Engine, Ice-E, Ice Touch, and Network Your Software are trademarks or registered trademarks of ZeroC, Inc. and/or its affiliates. Other names appearing on the Site may be trademarks of their respective owners.
19. Contact Information
If you have any questions regarding these Terms of Use, please contact ZeroC.
